Guide to the Gerard Malanga Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 2008 acquisition, 1970-1997; 2; (2 boxes)
  - "#144 Luci Lawton, Red Hook, Bklyn, 30:vi:89", 1989 (Box 125)
  - "#145 Antonia Small / Marcus Schmid, Laurie McLeod / Barrington Ballet, Mass.", 1990 (Box 125)
  - "#146 Natasha", 1995 (Box 125)
  - "John Chamberlain, Sculptor", 1976 (Box 125)
- September 2009 acquisition, 1930s-2008; 18.68; (31 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  Organized into six subseries: I. Correspondence. II. Research for Scopophilia. III. Writings, Research, and Professional Files. IV. Printed Material. V. Family Papers. VI. Artwork.
  Boxes 154-155 (Audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  The September 2009 Acquisition contains professional and personal files, including correspondence, research material relating to Scopophilia and other projects, drafts of writings, printed material, and family papers.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1225.
  Purchased from Photo Anonyme Ltd. on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2009.
  - Correspondence, 2002-2008
    - General Correspondence, 2002-2007
      - Miscellaneous, 2003-2007; 10 (Box 126)
      - Archive File, 2002-2007; 4 (Box 126)
      - Archive File, 2002-2007; (6 folders, 1 compact disc) (Box 127)
    - Postal Time Capsule, 2006-2008; (7 folders, 1 compact disc) (Box 127)
      Includes copies of the 8 December 2007 edition of The Armenian Reporter and "Portrait of a Playwright: The Jackie Curtis Story" by Tom Weigel (2007)
    - Postal Time Capsule, 2006-2008; 5 (Box 128)
  - Research for Scopophilia, 1968-2007
    This subseries contains material relating to Malanga's research for the book he edited on voyeurism in photography, Scopophilia: The Love of Looking (1985). Material includes clippings and tearsheets from various sources, as well as correspondence, video and audio recordings, and photographs.
    - Plastic folder, undated; 2 (Box 128)
      Includes a VHS called "Mellow Mail: Lingerie Video Volume 3", a deck of sealed erotic playing cards containing vintage pictures, and clippings and pamphlets regarding nudity and erotica.
    - The World's Best Dirty Jokes, by Mr. J., 1976 (Box 128)
    - Gerard Malanga, press clippings, 1993 April (Box 128)
    - Sex in the Movies, clippings, 1988-1995, undated (Box 128)
    - Steiff Teddy Bears, clippings, 1985-1990, undated (Box 128)
    - Tartans / Plaids, 1984-1994, undated (Box 128)
    - Freud, Sigmund -- etc., 1982-1995, undated (Box 128)
    - Dr. Bruno Bettelheim, 1989-1990, undated (Box 128)
    - Milan Kundera, novelist, 1982-1984, undated (Box 128)
    - Marguerite Duras, clippings, 1992, undated (Box 128)
    - Naturalist / Nudist material, 1980s (Box 128)
    - Future Sex, magazine, issue 5, 1993 (Box 128)
    - Bob Guccione / Penthouse, clippings, 1990s (Box 128)
    - Aperture - Sex Issue, 1990 (Box 128)
    - Helmut Newton, photographer, undated; 2 (Box 128)
    - David Hamilton, photographer, undated (Box 128)
    - Bill Brandt, photographer, 1983-1987, undated (Box 128)
    - Sir Kenneth Clark, Art Historian, 1983, undated (Box 128)
    - Artist & Model, 1986, undated (Box 128)
    - Fort Lauderdale, Florida, 1983, 1985 (Box 128)
    - Swimming Hall of Fame, 1986 (Box 128)
    - Voyeurism research, etc., 1980s-1990s (Box 128)
    - Scopophilia by Gerard Malanga - re: information, reviews, etc., 1986-1992, undated (Box 128)
    - Photography books, 1991 January 4 (Box 128)
    - Exhibitions & exhibit reviews, 1980s-1990s (Box 128)
    - Gallery exhibitions of the nude, undated (Box 128)
    - Playboy tearsheets, undated (Box 128)
    - Lingerie clippings, undated (Box 128)
    - Fashion - the body, etc., 1994, undated (Box 128)
    - Ads dealing with sexuality, etc., undated (Box 128)
    - Barry Savenor artifact, 1990, undated (Box 128)
    - Vladimir Nabokov, 1970s-1980s (Box 128)
    - Roman Polanski, filmmaker, 1993-1994, undated (Box 129)
    - Perfume / Scent / Sweat / Oder / Smell, undated (Box 129)
    - Cindy Crawford, 1989-1995, undated (Box 129)
    - Francesca Woodman, photographer, 1986, 1993 (Box 129)
    - Jock Sturges, 1982-1994, undated (Box 129)
    - Lawrence Stanley, 1991-1993 (Box 129)
    - Jane Seymour, 1981-1982, undated (Box 129)
    - ISNA / InterSex Society of North America, 1990s (Box 129)
    - Fetish & Taboo, undated (Box 129)
    - Henry and June / The Movie, 1990-1995, undated (Box 129)
    - Thomas Eakins, painter, 1994, undated (Box 129)
    - David Salle, painter, 1986-1994 (Box 129)
    - Erich Fischl, painter, 1986, undated (Box 129)
    - C. J. Scheiner, books, 1982-1993, undated (Box 129)
    - Tapestry Magazine, 1992 (Box 129)
    - Maurice Girodias / Olympia Press, 1974-1980, undated (Box 129)
    - Pornography - related tearsheets, 1990s (Box 129)
    - Censorship, etc., 1993 (Box 129)
    - Eroticism / Sexuality / The Nude, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 129)
    - 303 Park South - "Purity without Innocence, 1985", circa 1985 (Box 129)
    - Cap d'Agde, France, 1989; (1 folder, 1 5" reel to reel tape) (Box 129)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1980s-1990s (Box 129)
    - Joel Peter Witkin, 1993, undated (Box 129)
    - Breasts, undated (Box 129)
    - Masturbation, 1993 May (Box 129)
    - Health & Culture, undated (Box 129)
    - Nude beaches, 1970s-1990s (Box 129)
    - "Purity without Innocence," exhibit, 5 (Box 129)
    - Photovoyeurism - Lustrum Press, undated (Box 129)
    - Three Diamonds - Letters, Black Sparrow press, 1990s (Box 129)
    - Zoom, magazine, 1970, 1980; 2 (Box 129)
    - International Center of Photography - Ninth Year Report, 1983 (Box 130)
    - Alfred Van Der Marck Editions, Autumn 1985 and Soul Music, by Tina L'hotsky, 1978, 1985 (Box 130)
    - M / E / A / N / I / N / G, vol #1, Editors: Susan Bee & Mira Schor, 1986 (Box 130)
    - Spiral binder with notes, undated (Box 130)
    - Locations and ideas book, journal with clippings, undated (Box 130)
    - "Three Diamonds," photocopy book and writings, undated (Box 130)
    - Vis-a-Vis, no. 14, periodical, 1993 (Box 131)
    - Everyday Life: In Camera, 1987 March (Box 131)
    - Camera, no. 9, periodical, 1981 September (Box 131)
    - Crazy Spanish Girls, by Tina Lhotsky, 1978 (Box 131)
    - Camera, no. 9, periodical, 1972 September (Box 131)
    - Photo Communique, periodical, 1980 (Box 131)
    - Fig Leaves: The Journal of Discivilization, periodical, 1986 (Box 131)
    - Photo Review, vol. 11, no. 4, 1988 (Box 131)
    - The Event, issue 32, periodical, 1989 (Box 131)
    - Shooting the Nude, periodical, 1980 November (Box 131)
    - Photo / Design: For The Creative Team, 2007 (Box 131)
    - Photography Center Quarterly #59 Artists Who Mend, periodical, 1994 (Box 131)
    - Chelsea Hotel: A Magazine for the Arts, vol. 2, periodical, circa 1994 (Box 131)
    - Stern Magazin, periodical, 1989 (Box 131)
    - Sex, Performance and The 80s: Franklin Furnance, The Flue. Double Issue, 1982 (Box 131)
    - Victoria's Secret: Christmas 1993, catalog (Box 131)
    - Nude, by John Hersey, 1991 (Box 131)
    - Facts about Nudism, by Hugh Morris, 1966 (Box 131)
    - Maledicta, vol. VI, journal, 1982 (Box 131)
    - Genevieve Naturisme: 1991 Season, catalog (Box 131)
    - Psychology Evolution Psychosomatics: John Gach Books, catalogs, 1984-1987 (Box 131)
    - Palm Beach Photographic Workshops, catalog, 1989 (Box 131)
    - Max, periodical, 1992 April (Box 131)
    - National Geographic, periodical, 1979 June (Box 131)
    - Mizue, periodical, 1988 (Box 131)
    - Vogue Italia, periodical, 1994 February (Box 131)
    - Rockin' On, vol. 2, periodical, 1994 August (Box 131)
    - Vanity Fair, periodical, 1993 December (Box 131)
    - Flash Art: The Largest European Art Magazine, periodical, 1982 May (Box 131)
    - Photo World, periodical, 1974 May (Box 131)
    - People Weekly, periodical, 1993 October (Box 131)
    - Playboy, periodical, 1990 June (Box 131a)
    - Photo, periodical, 1977 March (Box 131a)
    - Vogue, periodical, 1994 January (Box 131a)
    - Playboy, periodical, 1994 January (Box 131a)
    - Janus 23, periodical, 1980, 1983; 2 (Box 131a)
    - Yellow Silk, Erotic Arts, vol. 5, periodical, 1989 (Box 131a)
    - Bad Attitudes, vol. 5, no.1, periodial, 1989 (Box 131a)
    - On Our Backs, periodical, 1989 (Box 131a)
    - Lui, periodical, 1986 (Box 131a)
    - Interviu, periodical, 1986 June 24 (Box 131a)
    - Rolling Stone, periodical, 1993-1994; 2 (Box 131a)
    - American Photo, periodical, 1993 (Box 131a)
    - Exposure 20:4, periodical, 1982 (Box 131a)
    - Photo-Reporter, periodical, 1982 December (Box 131a)
    - SF Camerawork Quarterly, vol. 17, no. 2, periodical, 1990 (Box 131a)
    - Rockin' On, vol. 1, periodical, 1994 May (Box 131a)
    - Perspektief, no. 12, periodical, 1982 (Box 131a)
    - Alternative Media, periodical, 1983 (Box 131a)
    - Material removed from books, 19 (Box 132)
      Includes manuscript material removed from books transferred to Printed Acquisitions
  - Writings, Research, and Professional Files, 1930s-2008
    - Viennale - 2006 (Box 133)
    - Charles Henri Ford / Arena Editions, 2000, undated (Box 133)
    - Gary Graham poem & working drafts, 2000, undated (Box 133)
    - "The Taking of Grozny," working drafts, 7:II:2000 (Box 133)
    - Poem for Hoe, notes and drafts, 1999-2000 (Box 133)
    - Millenium poems - notes, 1999 (Box 133)
    - Kosovo, 1999 (Box 133)
    - Film Lab information, 1987-1990, undated (Box 133)
    - Carolee Schneemann, 2000, undated (Box 133)
    - Fred McDarrah and related issues, 1998-2002, undated (Box 133)
    - Ann Powell / Dewart Gleason, 2000 (Box 133)
    - Revolving copies, undated (Box 133)
    - Original poem, typescripts, 1980s-1990s (Box 133)
    - Cinematheque Ontario - Toronto, 1998-2006; 3 (Box 133)
    - Poem drafts, 1990-1991 (Box 133)
    - Master copies, 1998-2000 (Box 133)
    - Copies from masters, undated (Box 133)
    - 812 Warren St. Hudson, NY - Gerard's Apt., Aug.-Nov. 2006 (Box 133)
    - Plexifilm packet, 2003 (Box 133)
    - Michael Germini / Xenon Productions, 1995 (Box 133)
    - Grants research and one NEA 1990 rejection, 1989-1993; 3 (Box 133)
    - Lewis MacAdams, 1999-2001 (Box 133)
    - Malanga ephemera, 1991-2002 (Box 133)
    - Assorted correspondence, 2001-2003; 2 (Box 133)
    - Real estate, 2002 (Box 133)
    - John Thaw, actor, undated (Box 133)
    - Museum ephemera, 2002, undated (Box 133)
    - The High Line, 2000, undated (Box 133)
    - Jules Buis / Re: Belgium Poetry Prize, 2002, undated (Box 133)
    - John Martin / Black Sparrow Press, 2002, undated (Box 133)
    - Financial correspondence, 1999 (Box 133)
    - Monaco packet, 2003 (Box 133)
    - "Ernest Hemingway's Famous Lost Manuscripts, ca 1922," working drafts, 2000 (Box 134)
    - Storie / Roberto Santoro, Rome Italy, 2000 November (Box 134)
    - GM: Dagon James Interview, undated (Box 134)
    - Book dummy inserts, undated (Box 134)
    - Working drafts - "Leaving New York", undated (Box 134)
    - Julien Mérieau's History of Photography, working drafts, 2000 March (Box 134)
    - "The Holy Grail" - working drafts, 2002 (Box 134)
    - GM: Amiri, working drafts, 2002 (Box 134)
    - Poem to Lee Harwood, working drafts, 2000 (Box 134)
    - "Take 2" - working drafts, 2003 (Box 134)
    - Malanga - C.V., undated (Box 134)
    - Sarah Greenleaf Whittier and Mixed Bag, 1979-1996, undated (Box 134)
    - Botanique consignment sheets, undated (Box 134)
    - Gallery consignment sheets, 1990s; 2 (Box 134)
    - Bookings, 1999 (Box 134)
    - Rubber stamps, undated (Box 134)
    - Walker Art Center, authorization form, 2001 September (Box 134)
    - Steidl / Lawsuit, etc., 1997-1998 (Box 134)
    - Peter K. Wehrli / Steidl, undated (Box 134)
    - Marc Parent for Steidl, 1997-1998; 2 (Box 134)
    - NY FDN for the Arts, 2000 (Box 134)
    - Red Bass ephemera, circa 1991 (Box 134)
    - Charles Henri Ford drafts to preface for his photographs / Arena Editions, 2002, undated (Box 134)
    - Andy's Orbit: photos and text, 1983 (Box 134)
    - Who's There? poems, 2004 (Box 134)
    - Villa Tugendhat, poem for Martin Borowski, 2005-2007; 2 (Box 134)
    - Copies of poems submitted to "Voices in Italian Americana", 2004-2006 (Box 134)
    - Jackally Jill - NYC, 2003-2008 (Box 134)
    - Velvet Underground, 2002, undated (Box 134)
    - Andy Warhol, photocopies, undated (Box 134)
    - East Village art scene from the late 70s-80s, 2004-2005, undated (Box 134)
    - Paris Review and other print outs, 2006-2008, undated (Box 134)
    - 9th Poetry Series - starting 9/4/2007 (Box 134)
    - 8th Poetry Series, 2006-2008 (Box 134)
    - Bob Dylan footage, 2005 (Box 134)
    - MOJO London / Paul Trynka, 2000 May (Box 135)
    - American Express correspondence and financial information, 1999 (Box 135)
    - Advertisement clippings and Bedat & Co. catalog, 1999 (Box 135)
    - Bukowski and pictures, material, 1999 (Box 135)
    - Rain Taxi, correspondence, 2000 (Box 135)
    - Various East Village photographs and contact prints, undated (Box 135)
    - Tearsheets / movies, 1990-1992, undated (Box 135)
    - Andy Warhol's Brillo Boxes, symposium / Neurnberg, Germany, 1999 November (Box 135)
    - Carine Fol / Le Botanique - Philippe Franck / Tanscultures, 1999 June; 2 (Box 135)
    - Le Botanique, 1999 (Box 135)
    - Apartments, New York City, 1996-2000 (Box 135)
    - Clippings, photocopies and postcards, regarding Scopophilia, undated (Box 135)
    - Apartments, 2001-2002 (Box 135)
    - Various poems, undated; 2 (Box 135)
    - E-mail transmissions, 1999-2000; 2 (Box 135)
    - Ursule Molinaro, 1915?-2000, working drafts, undated (Box 135)
    - "The French Sledges," working drafts starting 17:i:2000 (Box 135)
    - "The French Dredges," working drafts, 2000 December (Box 135)
    - Reva Wolf / SUNY New Paltz - Symposium on "Andy Warhol's - Posthumous Reputation," 11:xi:99, 1999 (Box 135)
    - Starting out in the Sixties: The Selected Essays of Aram Saroyan, 2000, undated (Box 135)
    - Pennytruex Archival Project, 1998 (Box 135)
    - World Aids Day, 2000 (Box 135)
    - Publication correspondence, 2000-2002; 3 (Box 135)
    - Ever Feel Like You've Been Cheated, undated (Box 135)
    - Mauricio Pudiha, correspondence, 1999 (Box 135)
    - Calliope, 1999 (Box 135)
    - Alice Neel exhibition - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 2000 (Box 136)
    - Uniphoto - Tokyo, 2000 (Box 136)
    - JVC / Victor - Tokyo, 2000 (Box 136)
    - Chiat Day, 1990s (Box 136)
    - GQ Japan / Naoko Kisugi, 2000 (Box 136)
    - Photocopies of Malanga photographs, undated (Box 136)
    - Makoto Ohrui, correspondence, 2000 (Box 136)
    - Pregnant Women Project, 2000 (Box 136)
    - "After Paul Bowles, Charles Henri Ford," working drafts, 20:xi:99, 1999-2002 (Box 136)
    - "The Bowery Station," working drafts beginning 28:I:2000 (Box 136)
    - Man Ray, undated (Box 136)
    - Erik Laprade's interview w/ Gerard, 2003-2004 (Box 136)
    - Charles Henri Ford / Arena Editions, undated (Box 136)
    - "Untitled," working drafts, Shelter Island, 2000 (Box 136)
    - An early draft of "The Snowy Owl Shudders", undated (Box 136)
    - Lou Lou and What Came After Roam: works by Malanga, 1968 (Box 136)
    - Bill Wadsworth, poet, 2004 March (Box 136)
    - Publication correspondence, 1999-2001; 3 (Box 136)
    - Paris Review correspondence, 2002 (Box 136)
    - Publication correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 136)
    - Tsuyoshi Karrasoe with Gerard Malanga email exchange, 2004 (Box 136)
    - Bosnia mss / tearsheets, etc., 1997-1999, undated; 3 (Box 136)
    - Questions for Charles Henri Ford that didn't happen, 2001 (Box 136)
    - Drafts of Amiri Baraka poem, undated (Box 136)
    - Drafts for Ted Berrigan poem, undated (Box 136)
    - GM: "In the Shadow of the 3rd Ave El," signed copy, undated (Box 136)
    - Real Estate - Charlotteville, NY, 2008 (Box 136)
    - Publication correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 136)
    - Publication correspondence and clippings, 2004 (Box 136)
    - César Vallejo poems, typescript, 2004 (Box 136)
    - Robert Pyman exhibit with 1930s postcards, 1930s, 2002 (Box 136)
    - Workbench: Where Gerard's original bookcases come from, 1996, 2003 (Box 136)
    - Archiving Warhol
      - Supplementary Material, 2001-2002; 3 (Box 137)
      - Copyright and permissions where warranted, 2001-2002 (Box 137)
      - #1: Andy Warhol interview, undated (Box 137)
      - #3: The First Screen Test & 3-Minutes B&W Silent, undated (Box 137)
      - #13: The Re-making of the Original Brillo Box, undated (Box 137)
      - #14: Dead Warhol, undated (Box 137)
      - #4: The Kiss, undated (Box 137)
      - Prefatory Note - drafts, undated (Box 137)
      - #11: Fritzy, 1969, undated (Box 137)
      - #5: The Empire State Building Is a Star!, undated (Box 137)
      - #8: The Warhol / Yale Lecture, undated (Box 137)
      - #2: Notes from a Non-Literary Life, undated (Box 137)
      - #XII: A Conversation with Andy Warhol, undated (Box 137)
      - #10: This Photo May Not Be -- etc. / Billy Name, 2002, undated (Box 137)
      - Photocopies of photographs, undated (Box 137)
      - Ancillary material, 2001, undated (Box 137)
      - Supplementary photographs, undated (Box 137)
      - Creation Books International, 2002 (Box 137)
      - #6: People Places Food & Art, undated (Box 137)
      - #7 Electric Chairs on Display in Toronto for First Time!, undated (Box 137)
      - #9: In Reply to a Request for a Statemeant on the Velvet Underground, undated (Box 137)
    - GM: Cristin Pasotti interview, 2004 (Box 137)
    - Texts to Malanga photographs, 1996, undated (Box 137)
    - Contract information - Centre Pomidou, 2002 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence - Tsuyoshi Kawasoe, 1999-2003 (Box 137)
    - Jeff Koons interview by Gerard Malanga - June 28, 2002 (Box 137)
    - John Solt, 1990-1996, undated (Box 137)
    - Tsuyoshi Kawasoe, 2000 (Box 137)
    - Interview with Gerard Malanga - H magazine - master copy, undated (Box 137)
    - Didier Devillez, editeur, 1998-1999 (Box 137)
    - GM: Letter to the Editor re Alan Riding, 1996 (Box 137)
    - Assorted correspondence, circa 1994-2003 (Box 137)
    - Loose notes, correspondence and flyers, 1998-2007, undated (Box 137)
    - Eldon Garnet, correspondence, 2003 (Box 137)
    - James Crump proposals, 2003 (Box 137)
    - Archiving Warhol, proof, circa 2001 (Box 137)
    - Eric La Prade's interview of Gerard Malanga, undated (Box 137)
    - Henry Ferrini re: Olson document, 2002-2003 (Box 137)
    - The Legacy of Gaile Vazbys, 1983; 2 (Box 137)
    - Typed drafts with marginal notes, undated (Box 137)
    - "Closed Files"
      - Warhol / Mastercard / Sotheby's, 2007 (Box 138)
      - Mark Webber, 2007 (Box 138)
      - Paris Review / GM Portfolio / 50th anniversary issue, 2002-2005, undated (Box 138)
      - Frank O. Braynard, 2004-2008, undated (Box 138)
      - Kazuo Ohno, 2006-2007, undated (Box 138)
        Includes photographs and exhibt catalogs
      - Christie's Warhol auction, 2007 (Box 138)
      - Martina Kudlacek e-mails and Alexander Hammid incidentals, 2002-2005, undated; 2 (Box 138)
      - Martina Kudlacek: Marie Menken movie, 2005-2007 (Box 138)
      - Beursschouwburg and Freddy Thielemans, Brussels, 2006-2007; 2 (Box 138)
      - Crossing Border Festival, 2007; 3 (Box 138)
      - Agnès B. exhibit, Paris, 2005-2007; 2 (Box 138)
      - Edie Sedgwick: "Factory Girl", 2004-2007; 2 (Box 138)
      - Interview w/ Gerard Malanga - LID, 2004; 2 (Box 138)
      - Lou Reed / Connections, 2008 (Box 138)
      - Andrew Wylie, 2 Sets Prototypes for Dice Poems, circa 1972 (Box 138)
      - Don Snyder, photographer, 2007 (Box 138)
      - Chuck Goldman / Daisy Aldan, 2007 (Box 138)
      - VH1 Warhol Project, 2008 (Box 138)
  - Printed Material, 1977-2008
    - Gerard Malanga: Screen Tests, Portraits, Nudes 1964-1996, Steidl catalog, 1990s (Box 139)
    - Asako's T-shirt design, 2003 September 8 (Box 139)
    - Conjunctions mag, financial and correspondence, 2004 (Box 139)
    - Arena promotions, 2000 (Box 139)
    - It Was Twenty Years Ago Today, Derek Taylor publicity, 1987 (Box 139)
    - Publicity material, 1993-2007 (Box 139)
    - The America Poetry Review, 1991 (Box 139)
    - Rolling Stone magazine, 1997; 2 (Box 139)
    - Interview magazine, 2008 November (Box 139)
    - Legal Affairs magazine, 2005 (Box 139)
    - Steidl catalogs, with Steidl correspondence and paperwork, 1998-2002 (Box 139)
    - IPSO FACTO Publishers NYC catalog, 1999 (Box 139)
    - Printed publicity material, circa 1992-2007 (Box 140)
    - Poetry reading at Hell's Gate, Vicoria Platz, publicity cards, 1992 (Box 140)
    - Periodicals, 1998-2002 (Box 140)
    - International publicity material, 1994-2007, undated; 2 (Box 140)
    - Periodicals, 1997-2008; 3 (Box 140)
    - Publicity materials, 2005-2007 (Box 140)
    - All Tomorrow's Parties, 2002 (Box 140)
    - Publicity materials and photographs, 2004-2007 (Box 140)
    - Art periodicals, 1997-2007; 3 (Box 140)
    - Christie's catalog, 2008 November 13 (Box 140)
    - Publicity materials - "The Cats in my Life", 2008 (Box 140)
    - Periodicals, 1992-2008; 2 (Box 140)
    - Materials related to Bringing Up Baby, 1977; 2 (Box 140)
    - Band À Part - Agnès B., press kit, undated (Box 141)
    - T-shirts from "Poetry of Sex" and "Andy Warhol: Work and Play", undated (Box 142)
  - Family Papers, 1970s-1997
    This subseries consists of material relating to Gerard Malanga's mother, Emma (née Lovetree) Malanga. Included are correspondence, audio recordings, and legal and financial documents relating to a fraud committed against her, as well as materials documenting her funeral arrangements, death, and memorial service.
    - Emma Malanga funeral arrangments, 1970s-1988 (Box 143)
    - Invitation to dementia study, 1996 (Box 143)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 143)
    - Exhibits regarding fraud committed against Emma Malanga, 1986 (Box 143)
    - Envelope containing memorial cards and Emma Malanga memorial booklet, 1997 (Box 143)
    - Memories book for Emma Malanga, 1997 (Box 143)
    - Memorial book and papers regarding Emma Malanga's death, undated (Box 143)
    - Telephone and address book, undated (Box 143)
    - Papers regarding Emma Malanga, 1970s-1990s (Box 143)
    - Papers relating to fraud committed against Emma Malanga, 1976-1992 (Box 144)
    - Papers relating to Father, Gerardo Malanga, 1977-1987 (Box 144)
    - Emma Lovetree relating to fraud, 1997 (Box 144)
    - Papers regarding Emma Malanga's estate, 1996-1998; 3 (Box 144)
    - Personal effects, 1990, undated; (2 folders, 1 audiocassette) (Box 144)
      Includes Emma Malanga's ID card, bank books, keys, checkbooks, prayer books and an audio cassette of an interview with Emma Malanga and Annette O'Connor (circa 1990)
  - Oversize Material, 8
    - Printed material (from Research for Scopophilia ), 1980-1982; 2 (Box 145 (Oversize))
    - The Sixties, Rolling Stone (from Research for Scopophilia ), 1977 (Box 146 (Oversize))
    - Madonna: Nudes 1979, Taschen (from Research for Scopophilia ), 1996 (Box 146 (Oversize))
    - The Sixties: A Decade in Vogue, by Nicholas Drake (from Research for Scopophilia ), 1988 (Box 146 (Oversize))
    - Le Nu Français, by Jacques Laurent (from Research for Scopophilia ), 1982 (Box 146 (Oversize))
    - Avant Garde, periodical (from Research for Scopophilia ), 1968-1970; 3 (Box 147 (Oversize))
    - Erotix Photographs & Portraits of Women (from Writing, Research, and Professional Files), undated; 2 (Box 148 (Oversize))
    - Gerard Malanga: Erotix photographs (from Writing, Research, and Professional Files), undated (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - Closed Files - Box List, cardboard (from Writing, Research, and Professional Files), undated (Box 150 (Oversize))